[{"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "6比7()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "6比8()2", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "6比9()3", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "6比10()4", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "7比6()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "7比8()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "7比9()2", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "7比10()3", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "8比6()2", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "8比7()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "8比9()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "8比10()2", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "9比6()3", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "9比7()2", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "9比8()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "9比10()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "10比6()4", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "10比7()3", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "10比8()2", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-much", "title": "选一选", "stem": "10比9()1", "list": ["more", "less"]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-11-02"}]